Reister Ruedas

Antipolo, Calabarzon, Philippines



reister.ruedas@gmail.com



09493241618



linkedin.com/in/reisterruedas

Summary

I am an independent and self-motivated software engineer with a passion on developing web and mobile application, with substantial experiences in programming with cyber security in mind, have knowledge and skills in video editing and 3D modeling.

Experience



Cyber Security Student

ePLDT, Inc.

Feb 2022 - Present (5 months +)

- Monitor servers and devices using SIEM tools
- Report anomalies on the Infrastructure.
- Collaborate with other pillars of the company.

Mobile Application Developer

Makati City Government

Feb 2020 - Feb 2021 (1 year 1 month)

- Lead a team of 4 to develop a tourism mobile application
- Handled troubleshooting and debugging.
- Collaborated with business management and multimedia arts team.
- Contributed to the design and improvement of the user interface.
- Lead Developer

Education



Asia Pacific College

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering 2018 - 2022



🦄 Polytechnic University of the Philippines

Senior High School, Science, Technology, Engineering and Mathematics 2016 - 2018

Skills

Problem Solving • Analytical Skills • React is • React Native • REST APIs • HTML5 • CSS • Communication • Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC) • Teamwork

Honors & Awards



2nd Runner UP - Emerson Innovation Center

Nov 2019 https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/emerson-kick-starts-years-innovation-challenge-stem-camp-pioquinto/